groovejob.com 2010-06-26

# Site Privacy Policy

www.groovejob.com ("Site")

Privacy Statement test

We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This privacy policy applies to your information that we collect and receive; it does not apply to practices of businesses that we do not own or control or people we do not employ. At no time will we sell your information or release your personally-identifiable data without your permission. You can visit this Site without revealing who you are or providing any personal information about yourself.

By using this Site, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you use our services. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices.

This Site contains links to other sites. These include links to partners that we believe may be of interest to you. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Browsing the Site

If you browse through the Site without entering any personal data, we will gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and cannot be linked back to you unless you decide at some point to identify yourself. If you are only browsing, we collect the following information: IP address, the type of browser and operating system used to access our site, the date and time you access our site, the pages you visit (click-through), and if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website as well as additional information related to your visit. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Site.

Public Forums

We make message boards, chat rooms and other forums (the "Forums") available to our users and visitors. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personally identifying information there.

If you choose to transmit, submit or post information through the Forums, we will collect that information you provide. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law and pursuant to our Terms of Use.

Your Profile

The Site collects personally identifiable information from users when you create a profile or account, when you use certain products or services, and when you enter promotions or contests. Personal information is collected by specifically requesting it from you. We use this personal information only for the specific purpose specified at the time you input such information. For example, by using various features of the Site, we may need to collect your name, address, social security number, and telephone numbers. Email addresses, licensure, certifications, education, and/or employment history, dates available to travel, eligibility to work in the United States, legal history, other occupations and any comments related to this data. test

Since the Site is a career site, we give you the option of creating a profile and storing it in our database. You may use this profile to apply for a job online. Please note that once you submit your resume/profile to a potential employer, we and our affiliates disclaim all liability for distribution of your resume/profile data. Please refer to the Terms of Use for additional information on this topic.

You may remove your profile from our database at any time. However, employers and recruiters with whom you have applied for jobs may have retained a copy of your resume in their own files or database. We are not responsible for the retention, use, or privacy of resumes in these instances, or for the use or privacy of resumes by any of such parties.

Information Collected

We do not post our users' personal information for any reason. All users should be aware that when they display or distribute personal information that information can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties for which we are not responsible.

All information provided by users becomes the property of Internet Brands once received by us and may be used and disclosed as permitted in this Policy. 

We share your personal information with our affiliated companies in order to identify products or services in which you may have interest, to improve our user experience and generally to engage in market research and for other internal business purposes. We may also aggregate your personal information with others' information and prepare reports on site usage, purchase history or other factors for sale or distribution to others. Those reports are aggregated and include no personally identifying information. Finally, we may use your personal information to send you email or postal communications regarding products or services offered by us or by third parties with whom we have relationships in which we think you may be interested. We do not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties for unknown reasons.

You may at any time choose not to receive promotional emails from us by contacting us at [information@internetbrands.com](mailto:information@internetbrands.com). Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to this Site, as well as to facilitate, complete, or confirm any transaction that you may enter into or responding to your inquiry or request.

If you prefer for us not to provide your name and email or postal address to third parties for direct marketing purposes, please contact us at [information@internetbrands.com](mailto:information@internetbrands.com).

Cookies

We may place "cookies" on your personal computer. "Cookies" are small identifiers sent from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, similar to a license plate, that help us to recognize you if you visit our website again. Also, our site uses cookies to track how you found our site. Cookies are not designed to be used to get data from your hard drive, your e-mail or any other personal data about you. To protect your privacy we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings. Please note, however, that if you reject our cookies it is possible that some web pages may not properly load, your access to certain information might be denied or you might have to enter information about yourself more than once.

Security

This site has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

Third Party Advertising 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies use non-personally identifiable information regarding your visit to this website and other sites, such as the user IP address, pages viewed, date and time of your visit, and number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), to serve ads to you on this site and other sites that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

Specifically, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this website and other websites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

In addition, we use clear GIFs or pixel tags to help manage our online advertising. These clear GIFs enable our ad serving company to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site. This allows us to learn which banner ads bring users to our website. The information we collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable.

To learn more about these practice and your choices about not having this information used by these companies please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Contacting the Web Site

Please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do, we will update this Privacy Policy at our website, so be sure to check back here frequently.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

www.groovejob.com

March 24, 2009
